[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133baa8", "question": "What flavor of schnapps is used to make the drink Fuzzy Navel?", "answer": "Peach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea34ceff048f679a45aafc", "question": "Which is the oldest planet in our solar system?", "answer": "Jupiter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339948", "question": "What young actor played Forrest's son in the movie \"Forrest  Gump\"?", "answer": "Haley Joel Osment", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe765f7eec85e375820b27a", "question": "Which famous figures are featured on Prague\u2019s astronomical clock?", "answer": "The 12 Apostles", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7fa", "question": "At which university was the beverage Gatorade developed?", "answer": "University of Florida", "category": "general"}, {"id": "594a64302ebb971c1417fba1", "question": "In which US state would you find the \"Everglades\"?", "answer": "Florida", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "593c4b58b8198b9a2b077962", "question": "The film \"Casablanca\" takes place during which global conflict?", "answer": "World War II", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e9", "question": "Which \"Friends\" actress appeared in Bruce Springsteen's \"Dancing in the Dark\" video?", "answer": "Courtney Cox", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7ce67877e98cb97778a41", "question": "What is the oldest major city in the Philippines?", "answer": "Cebu", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339054", "question": "What was the name of Sherlock Holmes' intelligent brother?", "answer": "Mycroft", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dfc", "question": "What \"Family Feud\" actor ended up committing suicide?", "answer": "Ray Combs", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a285", "question": "Which Mike Judge-directed comedy featured the characters Peter Gibbons and Michael Bolton?", "answer": "Office Space", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fc5", "question": "Which detective story writer created the character Tuppence Beresford?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc51", "question": "What year was Marmite first launched onto the market?", "answer": "1902", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c751", "question": "What is the minimum number of sides required to create a Polygon?", "answer": "3", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59049e03cf93664eb10486b2", "question": "\"Friday the 13th motorcycle rally\" is held on every Friday the 13th in what Canadian city?", "answer": "Port Dover", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133920b", "question": "What early 1990's dance craze was launched by \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "The Bartman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a021", "question": "In the TV show \"Family Guy\", which member of the Griffin family is Herbert infatuated with?", "answer": "Chris", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8b2", "question": "In what city would you find Champ de Mars?", "answer": "Paris", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d47", "question": "What actress shaved her head for her role in the movie \"Empire Records\"?", "answer": "Robin Tunney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2f4", "question": "How many claws does a housecat have?", "answer": "Eighteen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff0b0cae662d71a53650fcc", "question": "What is the name of the magical map of Hogwarts School?", "answer": "Marauder's Map", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339da5", "question": "Who played the role of the US president in the movie \"Being There\"?", "answer": "Jack Warden", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a158", "question": "What is the street address of \"The Simpsons\" in the TV show by the same name?", "answer": "742 Evergreen Terrace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab99b3e21a8909e5c332d29", "question": "Who played the main female character in the 1939 film \"Destry Rides Again\"?", "answer": "Marlene Dietrich", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a700", "question": "Which US state is home to Great Sand Dunes National Monument?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fedd8a96ce05a3942286d72", "question": "What is the name of the highly-entertaining main villain of \"The Matrix\"?", "answer": "Agent Smith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ea", "question": "Excluding vowels with macrons, how many letters are in the Hawaiian alphabet?", "answer": "Twelve", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339181", "question": "Who was the female lead character in the movie \"Three Colors: White\"?", "answer": "Julie Delpy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b323608bf195a31e15d73b5", "question": "What character was invented to respond to questions from Gold Medal Flour customers?", "answer": "Betty Crocker", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd81dbed0de9af39e9d4692", "question": "Who was the first woman appointed to a president's cabinet?", "answer": "Frances Perkins", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4ec4a06d333868d34d763", "question": "What was the term for the official policy of racial segregation in South Africa until 1994?", "answer": "Apartheid", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5febb0f17e83c707845b210a", "question": "What is the technical name for having different-colored eyes?", "answer": "Heterchromia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b12c", "question": "Which Egyptian queen was married to pharaoh Akhenaten?", "answer": "Nefertiti", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3312ff048f679a45aaeb", "question": "What is the loudest animal on Earth?", "answer": "Sperm whale", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5af98437aeb0982ee455954a", "question": "Which Japanese Act sang the intro to the cartoon series \"Teen Titans\"?", "answer": "Puffy AmiYumi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fde", "question": "What 1959 Dave Brubeck Quartet piece borrows its name from its unusual time signature?", "answer": "Take Five", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba1a6874c93a3298b2129", "question": "What year did Jimmy Carter assume office as the 39th President of the United States?", "answer": "1977", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b953", "question": "In a game of basketball, how many players are on the court at one time?", "answer": "Ten", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd822e5d0de9af39e9d46ac", "question": "How many vice presidents did FDR have during his time in office?", "answer": "3", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b323302bf195a31e15d7396", "question": "Who is Woody Woodpecker's girlfriend?", "answer": "Winnie Woodpecker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390fb", "question": "Who wrote the 1994 novel \"The Fist of God\"?", "answer": "Frederick Forsyth", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b088", "question": "What year was the Hubble telescope launched into orbit?", "answer": "1990", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a3c839a039f3d7859290ffa", "question": "In the TV Show \"Gunsmoke\", who portrayed the blacksmith, Quint Asper?", "answer": "Burt Reynolds", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae8c", "question": "When did Arizona and New Mexico become states?", "answer": "1912", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c88e87222f44c2d77a29c47", "question": "Where is the deepest land gorge in the US?", "answer": "Along the border of eastern Oregon, eastern Washington and western Idaho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe773bceec85e375820b30c", "question": "How many \"emirates\" make up the United Arab Emirates?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e2d", "question": "Who is Ben Stiller's mother?", "answer": "Anne Meara", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f168fcf7c52aae91cc07cc", "question": "In what film did Elvis play a double role?", "answer": "Kissin' Cousins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd665bca5bfecdd737e0862", "question": "How long ago did mammoths go extinct?", "answer": "4000 years ago", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a14f", "question": "What city do Batman and Robin patrol?", "answer": "Gotham City", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab60", "question": "Prague is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Czech Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "592eb17cf83302ff91e464a8", "question": "What cartoon by Mike Judge is the 1999 film \"Office Space\" based on?", "answer": "Milton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e805afde59ea584496feab", "question": "Which UN Secretary-General was killed in an airplane crash in 1961?", "answer": "Dag Hammarskjold", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59067e18ff9c0647b50a8077", "question": "Who won the Men\u2019s Singles title at the 2016 Australian Open?", "answer": "Novak Djokovic", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a0c", "question": "Who played Khan in \"Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan\"?", "answer": "Ricardo Montalban", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be9a", "question": "What pro wrestler grew up next door to playwright Samuel Beckett?", "answer": "Andre the Giant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133957e", "question": "What game was played for money by the Vietnamese in \"The Deer Hunter\" movie?", "answer": "Russian Roulette", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c415", "question": "What animal produces most of the world's wool?", "answer": "Sheep", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58b8d7532b42d4a3561a9f0c", "question": "In which country would you find the Gruta Canabrava cave?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a53a", "question": "The city of Berkeley is located across a bay from what other city?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb30", "question": "What is your occupation if you are sometimes referred to as an apiarist?", "answer": "Beekeeper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7d1", "question": "What month's birthstone places highest on the Mohs scale?", "answer": "April's", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fffa6e873838c5c8a417f33", "question": "Which is the most dangerous tree in the world?", "answer": "Manchineel tree (Found in the Florida Everglades and coastal Caribbean, its sap will cause blisters with the slightest contact.)", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600cc8606de0eb824d4052fb", "question": "Where is the world's largest Roman aqueduct that is still in use?", "answer": "Spain -- The Segovia aqueduct, built in the first century A.D., carries water from the Fuente Fr\u00eda River to the city of Segovia.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a522", "question": "How many neighbors does Lesotho have?", "answer": "Only 1", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fede4396ce05a3942286dda", "question": "Which famous drummer was nicknamed \"The Beast\" while intoxicated?", "answer": "John Bonham", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601737dc44491cbd7c5a178f", "question": "Which national park is widely recognized as the world's first national park?", "answer": "Yellowstone National Park -- President\u00a0Ulysses S. Grant signed the law making Yellowstone a national park on March 1, 1872.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bca1", "question": "What Crayola color became \"midnight blue\" in 1958?", "answer": "Prussian blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4bf", "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Mauritania and Guinea-Bissau?", "answer": "Senegal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b831", "question": "What city is home to Amazon.com's headquarters?", "answer": "Seattle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad7", "question": "Hydrargyrum is an old name for which element on the periodic table?", "answer": "Mercury", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4af249076251badbeabe", "question": "Ruby Bridges became the first Black student to do what?", "answer": "At six-years-old, Ruby Bridges was the first Black child to be integrated into an all-white school in New Orleans in 1960.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3fe", "question": "The surface of the dwarf planet Pluto is made largely of what type of frozen gas?", "answer": "Methane", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4bba49076251badbeac7", "question": "How many rooms are there in Buckingham Palace (total number)?", "answer": "775 -- It includes 19 State rooms, 92 offices, 52 Royal and guest bedrooms, 188 bedrooms for staff and 78 bathrooms.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c657", "question": "How many horns does the average African black rhino have?", "answer": "Two", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58c89ce0011619dd6d415480", "question": "Under what name did Eric Cartman appear as a calculus teacher in an inner-city school in season 12?", "answer": "Eric Cartmenez", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bda8", "question": "What team's fans were inspired by the Rally Monkey?", "answer": "The Anaheim Angels", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d6af2596a59cbdfbd3ad", "question": "Which company released the first e-reader device?", "answer": "Barnes and Noble", "category": "general"}, {"id": "591c349c815febcc896f9253", "question": "On which of the Canary Island would you find the holiday destination of Corralejo?", "answer": "Fuerteventura", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe766bceec85e375820b288", "question": "In what Tahitian bay did Captain Cook first land?", "answer": "Matavai Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ea", "question": "Which US state is named after a King of England?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59774232284458f1d785441e", "question": "What church in Georgia has produced the films \"Flywheel\", \"Facing the Giants\", \"Fireproof\", \"Courageous\",and \"War Room\"?", "answer": "Sherwood Baptist Church, Albany, Georgia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4ecbf06d333868d34d767", "question": "What was the first cash crop in America?", "answer": "Tobacco", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7d1", "question": "What distance did the Romans once define as a thousand paces?", "answer": "A mile", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96a1823c87fd04dd15e0f", "question": "Who was the youngest declared monarch in history?", "answer": "Mary, Queen Scots", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feccd25ec223966ae8f88a9", "question": "Who was the first Disney princess with a tattoo?", "answer": "Pocahontas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fbae7ab0738315b1fb74e26", "question": "What mathematician published \"Elements\" and influenced the study of modern geometry?", "answer": "Euclid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7342beec85e375820b22f", "question": "Which U.S. aircraft carrier was lost during the Battle of the Coral Sea?", "answer": "The USS Lexington", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca33", "question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Pt?", "answer": "Platinum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5e5", "question": "The Khyber pass joins which\u00a0two countries?", "answer": "Afghanistan and Pakistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133926a", "question": "What movie follows the ins and outs of Lester Burnham's mid-life crisis?", "answer": "American Beauty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea4810ff048f679a45abae", "question": "What is the first priority in a trauma code?", "answer": "Airway", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5f95b2ca55722f97b22684df", "question": "What color was Obi-Wan Kenobi's Lightsaber?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febb6487e83c707845b2126", "question": "Which fruit is essentially a clone of itself?", "answer": "Banana", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4ec2f06d333868d34d761", "question": "In which year was the White Australia Policy formally abolished?", "answer": "1972", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7352deec85e375820b246", "question": "Who was President Nixon's first vice president?", "answer": "Spiro T. Agnew", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa3823c73aa70ea0b70acf", "question": "What mode of transportation is Missouri named for?", "answer": "Canoe (An Illinois tribe's phrase for the area's people, \"ouemessourita,\" translates to \u201cwooden canoe people\".)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a894", "question": "What city is home to the Oriental Pearl Tower?", "answer": "Shanghai", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be6c", "question": "What is Ohio Stadium also known as?", "answer": "The Horseshoe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59068295ff9c0647b50a809e", "question": "On what streaming platform was Kanye West\u2019s \"The Life of Pablo\" album launched?", "answer": "Tidal", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339566", "question": "Who directed, The Christmas Kid\"?", "answer": "Sid PInk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddd", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"pundit\"?", "answer": "Hindi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd9", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"luau\"?", "answer": "Hawaiian", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339605", "question": "What name is given to the virus in the 2002 movie \"28 Days Later\"?", "answer": "The Rage Virus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fb5", "question": "In his Snake Plissken movies, what kind of snake is Kurt Russell's stomach tattoo?", "answer": "Cobra", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0ab", "question": "What kind of a head does a Hieracosphinx possess?", "answer": "Hawk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecdd21ec223966ae8f88ff", "question": "Who introduced Johnny Depp to acting?", "answer": "Nicolas Cage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e8", "question": "What does M.C. stand for in M.C. Escher's name?", "answer": "Maurits Cornelis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb5fec5dad637d903c8828", "question": "Lei Day is a special May Day celebration held in which of America's states?", "answer": "Hawaii", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5990f8dafa5fdd6dd25324f2", "question": "Where did we meet Newkirk, Carter, LeBeau and Kinchlow?", "answer": "Hogan's Heroes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58c8a84290aac110e416708d", "question": "Who said \"He that drinks his cider alone, let him catch his horse alone.\"?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7eb", "question": "Which two Great Lakes does the state of Wisconsin border?", "answer": "Lake Michigan and Lake Superior", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5c77cf2f24f0f7a362efd54c", "question": "How many claws in total does the average adult cat have?", "answer": "18", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a228", "question": "In what year was Puff Daddy's \"I'll Be Missing You\" song released?", "answer": "1997", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b64f", "question": "From which US university did Richard Nixon obtain a law degree?", "answer": "Duke", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb08", "question": "What newspaper was founded in 1889 by Charles H. Dow and Edward Jones?", "answer": "Wall Street Journal", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b8", "question": "To protest an unpopular tax, which US state's residents held the \"Whiskey Rebellion\" in 1794?", "answer": "Pennsylvania", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b41", "question": "Who turned all he touched to gold?", "answer": "King Midas", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3bf", "question": "How many stars appear on the Australian flag?", "answer": "Six", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc89", "question": "What NHL team's theme music is Aram Khachaturian's most famous composition?", "answer": "The Buffalo Sabres", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff51487ff04d658268c92e3", "question": "What Spartan king led a small army of 300 Spartans against a vastly superior Persian force in the Battle of Thermopylae?", "answer": "Leonidas, King of Sparta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339afd", "question": "Based on total pop chart success, what woman was named \"Artist of the Decade\" for the 1990's by Billboard magazine?", "answer": "Mariah Carey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5907225e3745b36be73039ff", "question": "According to Futurama, what holiday is celebrated on December 25th in the year 3,000?", "answer": "Xmas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecdcdcec223966ae8f88f9", "question": "What actor played the role of Margaret White in the 2013 film \"Carrie\"?", "answer": "Julianne Moore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe52fb81bf59ab7d2e38117", "question": "Where is Bank of America headquartered?", "answer": "Charlotte, North Carolina", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea8078ff048f679a45ac19", "question": "What extinct animal was the ancestor of cattle?", "answer": "Auroch", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7ba", "question": "How many meters is a lap in an official Olympic swimming pool?", "answer": "100", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a614", "question": "What is the capital of Nigeria?", "answer": "Abuja", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad8a", "question": "How long did Pope John Paul I serve?", "answer": "33 days", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339930", "question": "Who directed the Michael Jackson music videos for \"Thriller\" and \"Black and White\"?", "answer": "John Landis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339563", "question": "Bill Melendez directed which Christmas TV special?", "answer": "A Charlie Brown Christmas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b83", "question": "For what 2001 movie did Ron Howard win an Oscar for Best Director?", "answer": "A Beautiful Mind", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af2", "question": "What 1950's rock pioneer was portrayed by Lou Diamond Phillips in a 1987 film?", "answer": "Ritchie Valens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a963", "question": "What split up into Gondwanaland and Laurasia?", "answer": "Pangaea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133badf", "question": "Which book of the Bible follows Exodus?", "answer": "Leviticus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4ed3a06d333868d34d76b", "question": "The first TV commercial for a toy aired in 1952 featuring what toy?", "answer": "Mr. Potato Head", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aece", "question": "What was the second successful mass produced car by the Ford Motor Company called?", "answer": "Model A", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff1401eb0ee8c595b6d3995", "question": "Which painting was stolen from the Louvre in 1911 and not returned for over two years?", "answer": "The Mona Lisa", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d39", "question": "The co-creator of Superman, Joe Shuster, was born in which Canadian town?", "answer": "Toronto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133926d", "question": "Which rap star was born Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.?", "answer": "Snoop Dogg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594a62302ebb971c1417fb8d", "question": "Which French district does Claret come from?", "answer": "Bordeaux", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59523ec4736d4be723796b53", "question": "What three provinces requested a single Dominion be formed in 1867, thus beginning to shape modern Canada?", "answer": "New Brunswick, Nova Scotia and the Province of Canada", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133986f", "question": "In Disney's \"Peter Pan\", what is the name of the Chiefs daughter?", "answer": "Tiger Lily", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8bf", "question": "What three-mile-wide New Brunswick island was FDR's summer home?", "answer": "Campobello", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338885", "question": "What does a bibliophile enjoy?", "answer": "Books", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a73d", "question": "Hells Canyon is located in which two US states?", "answer": "Idaho and Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a424", "question": "In what state would you find the supposed UFO site named \"Area 51\"?", "answer": "Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b01f", "question": "What was the last name of husband and wife Julius and Ethel, executed for treason in 1953?", "answer": "Rosenberg", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59523ef3736d4be723796b55", "question": "What type of interchange, that is widely used in North America and in some parts of Europe, did the Ontario Ministry of Transportation invent?", "answer": "Partial cloverleaf interchange, or Parclo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7c716877e98cb977789c8", "question": "Where is the world\u2019s longest underwater cave?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea3590ff048f679a45ab04", "question": "What is so reactive with water that it has to be stored in oil because it will react with the air\u2019s moisture?", "answer": "Potassium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339166", "question": "What is the secret identity of Don Vito Corleone?", "answer": "The Godfather", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beba", "question": "What Thames River town lent its name to the collarless polo shirts first worn by its rowing team?", "answer": "Henley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339907", "question": "Brian Johnson is the lead singer of what rock band?", "answer": "AC/DC", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338de8", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"typhoon\"?", "answer": "Cantonese", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6fe", "question": "What decade was Girl Scouts of America formed in?", "answer": "1910s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0eb", "question": "Christopher Cockerell is best known for invented what?", "answer": "The hovercraft", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389ce", "question": "What Post-Impressionist painter of cabaret and brother life was dubbed the soul of Montmartre?", "answer": "Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febb5af7e83c707845b211f", "question": "What's the word for when you can't remember a word?", "answer": "Lethologica", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adfe", "question": "Which city hosted the Olympic Games in 2000?", "answer": "Sydney", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fd2", "question": "In Greek mythology, who did Hippomenes defeat in a footrace?", "answer": "Atalanta", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5cd40ca4685cf15b733e9890", "question": "How many furlongs are there in a mile?", "answer": "8", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6be", "question": "The Mississippi River flows into what body of water?", "answer": "Gulf of Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfd2", "question": "What is the NATO phonetic alphabet word for \"F\"?", "answer": "Foxtrot", "category": "general"}, {"id": "590679b5ff9c0647b50a8051", "question": "On January 1, 2016, which Canadian province became the first one to allow the testing of self-driving vehicles on public roads?", "answer": "Ontario", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe93ccf6bd93ce3a4e5f6ac", "question": "What is the smallest biological unit of a living organism?", "answer": "Cell", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5bb", "question": "What type of milk is traditional feta cheese made of?", "answer": "Sheep's milk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133988e", "question": "In the 1964 stop-motion TV special \"Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer\", who is Rudolph's father?", "answer": "Donner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b885e662d71a53651025", "question": "Which German painter was sometimes court painter to King Henry VIII of England after 1536?", "answer": "Hans Holbein the Younger", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6a9a120565ad31a57c808", "question": "Who issued the \"Emancipation Proclamation\"?", "answer": "President Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b22e", "question": "What brainchild of Wisconsin senator Gaylord Nelson was first celebrated on April 22, 1970?", "answer": "Earth Day", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b29b", "question": "What bird did Ben Franklin suggest replace the bald eagle as a national emblem?", "answer": "The wild turkey", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad9e232e748bb36357acdf9", "question": "What year did Alfred Hitchcock release his first American made film?", "answer": "1940", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b47a", "question": "The Battle of the Plains of Abraham was fought outside of which Canadian city?", "answer": "Quebec City", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b90", "question": "Where do you end up if you fly toward the second star to the right and then proceed straight on until morning?", "answer": "Neverland", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c667", "question": "What is the largest rodent in the US?", "answer": "The Beaver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5eb", "question": "What type of garment are \"Elephant bells\"?", "answer": "Pants", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a988", "question": "What city named its airport after John Foster Dulles?", "answer": "Washington, D.C.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc0f", "question": "What was Wayne Gretzky's jersey number during his professional hockey career?", "answer": "99", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa8b", "question": "Maseru is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Lesotho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60062c20c9d816e292245c29", "question": "English artist Andy Brown created a portrait of Queen Elizabeth II using what?", "answer": "English artist Andy Brown created a portrait of Queen Elizabeth II out of 1000 used and unused tea bags.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5902a06fcad1ec93f27df76c", "question": "Which Bohemian city gave us the Pilsner?", "answer": "Pilsen", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e2b", "question": "Who is Jamie Lee Curtis' mother?", "answer": "Janet Leigh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7ffaa83a3a814d89068c5d", "question": "In the 1988 film \"Twins\", what were the character names of Arnold Schwarzenneger and Danny De Vito?", "answer": "Julius and Vincent", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6d2", "question": "What decade were golf carts introduced in the US?", "answer": "1940s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d77", "question": "What classic novel's subtitle is \"The Children's Crusade\"?", "answer": "Slaughterhouse-Five", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5c3", "question": "What company was formerly known as the \"Computing-Tabulating-Recording Company\"?", "answer": "IBM", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febda227e83c707845b2181", "question": "Which American golfer was nicknamed \"The Joplin Ghost\"?", "answer": "Horton Smith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b712", "question": "Which New York newspaper wrote \"yes Virginia, there is a Santa Claus\"?", "answer": "The New York Sun", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb69", "question": "What tennis player was named \"Sexiest Woman in the World\" by FHM magazine in 2002?", "answer": "Anna Kournikova", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a84d", "question": "What sea borders Iran to the north?", "answer": "Caspian Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133965b", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of the Springfield Elementary lunchlady?", "answer": "Doris", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396b5", "question": "What movie features the line: \"You can't handle the truth\"?", "answer": "A Few Good Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a905", "question": "What major river runs through Vienna?", "answer": "Danube", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dc7", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by David Bowie?", "answer": "Rebel Rebel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c991", "question": "What is the young of a pigeon called?", "answer": "Squab", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe77014eec85e375820b2f4", "question": "Which body of water is the Nile River\u2019s primary reservoir?", "answer": "Lake Victoria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febd3c97e83c707845b2155", "question": "Which electronic musical instrument emits the eeriest of sounds and is the only instrument played without touching it?", "answer": "Theremin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca1c", "question": "What type of animal is a Borzoi?", "answer": "A dog", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8be", "question": "What two animals are the symbols of the US Democrats and Republicans?", "answer": "Donkey and Elephant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e9", "question": "What group's 1979 debut album was entitled \"Reproduction\"?", "answer": "Human League", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "596760912b59efe0e9417e9d", "question": "A baby oyster is called a what?", "answer": "A spat", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff13fa4b0ee8c595b6d3990", "question": "How long did it take Michelangelo to paint the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?", "answer": "4 years", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad5e", "question": "For what does the \"F.\" stand in the name F. Lee Bailey?", "answer": "Francis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392b8", "question": "Who directed the 1980 movie \"The Blues Brothers\"?", "answer": "John Landis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909cab7bb53d1af658864d1", "question": "On what short story was the 1946 film \"It\u2019s a Wonderful Life\" based on?", "answer": "The Greatest Gift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6a0", "question": "A cat-o'-nine tails is a type of what?", "answer": "Whip", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe3ee638b5801b8f54a7fb7", "question": "Which was the last major offensive operation undertaken by elite German paratroopers in World War II?", "answer": "Attack against Crete", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fec8bc5ec223966ae8f8842", "question": "Dr. Gregory House shares the same home address as which other fictional character?", "answer": "Sherlock Holmes (albeit in different countries)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc8b", "question": "Who did the Chicago Bears fire in 1992, just four years after he was the NFL Coach of the Year?", "answer": "Mike Ditka", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b083", "question": "In what year did \"Mad Magazine\" debut?", "answer": "1952", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc5e", "question": "Football player Pel\u00e9 was born in which Brazilian state?", "answer": "Minas Gerais", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f164ecef9b80650dbe7f938", "question": "What color is the \"Power stone\" in the 2017 Marvel Legacy relaunch?", "answer": "Purple", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e5", "question": "What were 2 out of 3 of Andrew Lloyd Webbers wives called?", "answer": "Sarah", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339091", "question": "In Greek mythology, what was Hades the god of?", "answer": "Underworld", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8af", "question": "St. Patrick's Day is celebrated on what day in March?", "answer": "17th", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133930a", "question": "In the 1982 movie \"E.T. The Extra-Terrestrial\", who plays Elliot's younger sister?", "answer": "Drew Barrymore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1e4", "question": "Which US president lived in Springwood?", "answer": "Franklin Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b23adf68f1a2238a7cb2b3a", "question": "In the novel series, \"A Series of Unfortunate Events\", who was the Baudelaire's sixth guardian?", "answer": "Jerome and Esme Squalor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a5f", "question": "What actor's character ran \"Blush\" magazine on the TV show \"Just Shoot Me\"?", "answer": "George Segal", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396a8", "question": "What MTV cartoon duo was created by Mike Judge?", "answer": "Beavis and Butthead", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a7f720565ad31a57c7f1", "question": "What President\u2019s fondness for pork rinds made sales of the snack boom?", "answer": "George H. W. Bush", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339912", "question": "Versacorp and Protege were the names of the two teams on the first season of what reality show?", "answer": "The Apprentice", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc714ec223966ae8f888a", "question": "Musician Peter Tork was a founding member of which 1960s band?", "answer": "The Monkeys", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7bc", "question": "What natural \"Wonder of the World\" lies off the east coast of Australia?", "answer": "The Great Barrier Reef", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe65952ae7e414034b5aefd", "question": "The Ottoman Turks captured Constantinople in what year?", "answer": "1453", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601b4c3049076251badbeacf", "question": "Which unique pet did Calvin Coolidge have during his presidency?", "answer": "Raccoon -- Named Rachel, she might be the most well known pet.  She walked around on a leash and was the master of mischief.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601b4a2e49076251badbeab0", "question": "Where did the phrase \"Don\u2019t Mess With Texas\" come from?", "answer": "An anti-litter campaign -- The campaign idea was \u201cdon\u2019t litter in Texas, don\u2019t mess up Texas,\u201d but it became so much more.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aff", "question": "Which character killed Jay Gatsby?", "answer": "George Wilson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fef5f566ce05a3942286e41", "question": "Who was the highest paid athlete of 2018?", "answer": "Floyd Mayweather", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339798", "question": "Who did Michael Jackson marry in May 1994?", "answer": "Lisa Marie Pressley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b457", "question": "What was the name of Hannibal's father?", "answer": "Hamilcar Barca", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb45", "question": "A hobbyist referred to as a \"numismatist\" studies or collects what?", "answer": "Coins", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaec", "question": "What is the capital of Tanzania?", "answer": "Dodoma", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010c8f30775fa611bce67e6", "question": "\"A capella\" is an Italian term that means what?", "answer": "\"In the manner of the chapel\" --  A capella music is a group or solo performance without instrumental accompaniment.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a65c", "question": "The port city of Sandusky is located in which state?", "answer": "Ohio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5909d2f6bb53d1af6588650e", "question": "Who played the lead role in the 1983 film \"Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba0", "question": "Barry Allen was the alter ego of which comic book superhero?", "answer": "The Flash", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5feddaff6ce05a3942286d8c", "question": "What store in Diagon Alley sells ingredients for potion making?", "answer": "The Apothecary", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601370f61381754895396387", "question": "Who said, \"We came, we saw, we kicked its ass\"?", "answer": "Dr. Peter Venkman in the film \"Ghostbusters\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f2d", "question": "Who wrote \"Our Lady of the Flowers\" while in prison?", "answer": "Jean Genet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd6a3236c0f9723ab15cb4a", "question": "What did Pocahontas change her name to after she converted to Christianity?", "answer": "Rebecca", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6010ca2e0775fa611bce67f4", "question": "Which famed beauty company was named in part for its founder's sister?", "answer": "Maybelline -- Thomas Lyle Williams developed a product for darkening eyebrows and eyelashes and named it after his sister Mabel.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4cb", "question": "What day did the Battle of the Somme begin?", "answer": "July 1, 1916", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cdcc1e347d002c297e4eb", "question": "President Richard Nixon called what songstress an \"Ambassador of Love\"?", "answer": "Pearl Baily", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c706", "question": "Who was the first American astronaut to orbit the Earth, circling it three times in 1962?", "answer": "John Glenn", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a60f", "question": "What is the alternative name for the Greek Island of Zakynthos?", "answer": "Zante", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2b3", "question": "In what ship's 1945 sinking were there as many as eighty sailors eaten by whitetip sharks?", "answer": "The USS Indianapolis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ff0", "question": "What was Walt Disney's middle name?", "answer": "Elias", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2bf", "question": "Who played the role of Tracy Jordan on the TV show \"30 Rock\"?", "answer": "Tracy Morgan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f5649133a95c66dc4fe74f", "question": "Roman Polanski directed which 1974 film starring Jack Nicholson?", "answer": "Chinatown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396b9", "question": "What candy does E.T. love?", "answer": "Reese's Pieces", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aed", "question": "What is Charlie's last name in Roald Dahl's \"Charlie and the Chocolate Factory\"?", "answer": "Bucket", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339127", "question": "What French composer wrote the opera \"Samson and Delilah\"?", "answer": "Camille Saint-Saens", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a50d", "question": "On which island is the Empire State Building located?", "answer": "Manhattan", "category": "geography"}]